{
    "id": "5f47524ab26e4c4189adfb24796b2724",
    "title": "Make, Allow, Force",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They ...................................... me repeat the whole story.",
            "description": "Made is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "allowed",
                "forced"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5481f1cd7c364531b6a548e4a8b3e91f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ..................................... me to leave his home.",
            "description": "Forced is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "forced"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0962804d150b4f91be5737a72110946b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was not ...................................... to meet them.",
            "description": "Allow is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "allowed",
                "forced"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3e5c6831004145bf98d8d6c5eb669e3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "They .......................................... me to give in.",
            "description": "To force is to compel.",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "allowed",
                "forced"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7cfacfe0b79441bf9a9d3d679d389190"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ....................................... to smoke in public places.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "allowed not",
                "are not allowed",
                "don't allow"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4c483efea64e452083c49651e6bfd81b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you .................................... me to sit here?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "force",
                "allow",
                "let"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a31de335f1cb4d36ae5f022be1156386"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ...................................... them go.",
            "description": "Let is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "allow",
                "let",
                "force"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b3165f00cff04ee689aefe8f5d78e97b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ....................................... to pay for the drinks.",
            "description": "Either could be used with little difference of meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "allowed",
                "forced",
                "made"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6a2dbc1e69584990981670b04fb2e0dd"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ............................................... to apologize to them.",
            "description": "Either could be used here",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "allowed",
                "forced"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c0a36a5ff1e3472592e63f836b4179ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "We do not .......................................... children to stay up late.",
            "description": "Allow is followed by an infinitive with to.",
            "answers": [
                "allow",
                "let",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ef854ea102540169cf9f6bcc5bd52c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He struggled to ........................................ himself understood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "allow",
                "force"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "47f8574eb0c24f858f2bc7f41064250e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was ………………………….. to visit them whenever I wanted to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "allowed",
                "forced"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9d73b1bbff14452b82ce84d5b8e06f4d"
        }
    ]
}